Kenny Becerra Programmer/ IT Analyst





About me

I am a programmer with a passion for front-end development. My background is in computer engineering and my technical career has centered around developing/managing tools for process improvement and automation. Checkout my github to see some of the Front-end dev projects I've worked on.



Skills

HTML/CSS		
✓ HTML5 ✓ Flexbox JAVASCRIPT	✓ CSS2/CSS3 ✓ Bootstrap	✓ SASS/LESS✓ Responsive Design
✓ ES5 ✓ AJAX TOOLS	✓ ES6 ✓ Jquery	✓ ES7
✓ NPM ✓ Grunt	✓ Webpack ✓ VS Code	✓ Gulp✓ Git Version Control



Work Experience

Programmer/ IT CyberSecurity Analyst at Pacific Gas & Electric

San Francisco, CA January 2017 - Present

Developed and maintained team systems and tools using VBA, SQL, HTML, CSS, and Javascript Developed SP Sites/Pages using Jquery/D3.js in order access/modify SP backend via REST Calls Utilized SQL, VBA, and javascript to enhance Team's system tools, automated reporting, and metrics Managed team repositories/tools in MS Access, SharePoint (SP), and MetricStream.

Programmer/IT Analyst at Pacific Gas & Electric

San Francisco, CA August 2015 - December 2016

Developed scripting solutions for Energy Procurement Support team Ad-hoc requests. Developed UI functionality for Energy Procurement System tools using SQL, and VBA. Automated administrative tasks and workflows using VBA, python and SharePoint Rest API

Software Engineering intern at General Electric

Waukesha, WI May 2014 - August 2014

Developed scripts in Lua and Python language for software testing and data manipulation Researched integration of DDS (Data Distribution Services) for CT Scanner middleware Evaluated integration methods of DDS and updated code information/manual



Education

Bachelors of Science in Computer **Engineering**

Florida State University



Contact



kennybecerra.j@gmail.com



https://github.com/kennybecerra



www.linkedin.com/in/kennybecerra/



https://kennybecerra.github.io/